Guide to the Douglas C. Engelbart Papers M0638
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Series 2. Accession 1998-094
  - Alphabetical Files, 1962-1991
    - Alpha Files A-Z 1981
      - Bamford, Jr. HE, 1981 (Box 37, Folder 1)
      - BEA, 1981 (Box 37, Folder 2)
      - Canadian Agency, 1981 (Box 37, Folder 3)
      - CIQT, 1981 (Box 37, Folder 4)
      - Citfix, 1981 (Box 37, Folder 5)
      - CMG, 1981 (Box 37, Folder 6)
      - CSEQ, 1981 (Box 37, Folder 7)
      - CTR Manager Group, 1981 (Box 37, Folder 8)
      - Current Work, 1981 (Box 37, Folder 9)
      - DARPA, 1981 (Box 37, Folder 10)
      - DBMS, 1981 (Box 37, Folder 11)
      - Diebold, 1981 (Box 37, Folder 12)
      - DOC-DPCS, 1981 (Box 37, Folder 13)
      - Document Editing Systems, 1981 (Box 37, Folder 14)
      - DSS NP, 1981 (Box 37, Folder 15)
      - E-Temp, 1981 (Box 37, Folder 16)
      - Emergency Management, 1981 (Box 37, Folder 17)
      - Ext Directive Sys, 1981 (Box 37, Folder 18)
      - Format, Org, 1981 (Box 37, Folder 19)
      - HPOD, 1981 (Box 37, Folder 20)
      - Intel System Architecture, 1981 (Box 37, Folder 21)
      - IRD-Rep, 1981 (Box 37, Folder 22)
      - Jan & Sue, 1981 (Box 37, Folder 23)
      - Journal, New, 1981 (Box 37, Folder 24)
      - JPL, 1981 (Box 37, Folder 25)
      - JTAB, 1981 (Box 37, Folder 26)
      - J/X, 1981 (Box 37, Folder 27)
      - Mail, 1981 (Box 37, Folder 28)
      - Magnum IQL Spec, 1981 (Box 37, Folder 29)
      - Many to Many Communication, 1981 (Box 37, Folder 30)
      - Markers, 1981 (Box 37, Folder 31)
      - Methodology, 1981 (Box 37, Folder 32)
      - N-Mail, 1981 (Box 37, Folder 33)
      - Notebooks, 1981 (Box 37, Folder 34)
      - NP Report, 1981 (Box 37, Folder 35)
      - NSF, 1981 (Box 37, Folder 36)
      - Org Network Services, 1981 (Box 37, Folder 37)
      - PC Communication Program, 1981 (Box 37, Folder 38)
      - PDPCS, 1981 (Box 37, Folder 39)
      - PLS, 1981 (Box 37, Folder 40)
      - Profile Sys, 1981 (Box 37, Folder 41)
      - Programming in L10, 1981 (Box 37, Folder 42)
      - P-XDOC, 1981 (Box 37, Folder 43)
      - Ref. A, 1981 (Box 37, Folder 44)
      - RINS Input, 1981 (Box 37, Folder 45)
      - Slide System, 1981 (Box 37, Folder 46)
      - Smalltalk, 1981 (Box 37, Folder 47)
      - Speech, 1981 (Box 37, Folder 48)
      - Stradis, 1981 (Box 37, Folder 49)
      - Subnet, 1981 (Box 37, Folder 50)
      - Sys Dialog, 1981 (Box 37, Folder 51)
      - TD Grist, 1981 (Box 37, Folder 52)
      - Tie-On, Etc., 1981 (Box 37, Folder 53)
      - To Work, 1981 (Box 37, Folder 54)
      - Trip, 1981 (Box 37, Folder 55)
      - Trial Text, 1981 (Box 37, Folder 56)
      - T-S, 1981 (Box 37, Folder 57)
      - TSUG, 1981 (Box 37, Folder 58)
      - Tymshare Users Group, 1981 (Box 37, Folder 59)
      - Van Dam, Andy, 1981 (Box 37, Folder 60)
      - Washington Contact Records, 1981 (Box 37, Folder 61)
      - XDT Grist, 1981 (Box 37, Folder 62)
      - X-Entry, Ready, 1981 (Box 37, Folder 63)
    - Alpha Files A-Z 1982
      - Misc. Unfiled, 1982 (Box 32, Folder 33)
      - AFIPS, 1982 (Box 32, Folder 34)
      - Augment, 1982 (Box 32, Folder 35)
      - Barratt, Stephanie, 1982 (Box 32, Folder 36)
      - Callender, ED, 1982 (Box 32, Folder 37)
      - Command Sequences, 1982 (Box 32, Folder 38)
      - CMG, 1982 (Box 32, Folder 39)
      - CMS, 1982 (Box 32, Folder 40)
      - C SEQ, 1982 (Box 32, Folder 41)
      - Design for Star User Interface, 1982 (Box 32, Folder 42)
      - Diebold, 1982 (Box 32, Folder 43)
      - Disk Directories, 1982 (Box 32, Folder 44)
      - Erik & Sven, 1982 (Box 32, Folder 45)
      - File Management, 1982 (Box 32, Folder 46)
      - Form 10-K, 1982 (Box 32, Folder 47)
      - Frantz Slide, 1982 (Box 32, Folder 48)
      - Graphic Font, 1982 (Box 32, Folder 49)
      - Graphics NP, 1982 (Box 32, Folder 50)
      - Grist, 1982 (Box 32, Folder 51)
      - Hower, Paul, 1982 (Box 32, Folder 52)
      - IBM, 1982 (Box 32, Folder 53)
      - Info Tech & Org, 1982 (Box 32, Folder 54)
      - I-Prog, 1982 (Box 32, Folder 55)
      - Japan, 1982 (Box 32, Folder 56)
      - Kummunedata, 1982 (Box 32, Folder 57)
      - Linking - Viewing, 1982 (Box 33, Folder 1)
      - Mitchell Pub, 1982 (Box 33, Folder 2)
      - NP Grist, 1982 (Box 33, Folder 3)
      - NSF, 1982 (Box 33, Folder 4)
      - Office Technology, 1982 (Box 33, Folder 5)
      - 1-2-3, 1982 (Box 33, Folder 6)
      - PC Basic Listing, 1982 (Box 33, Folder 7)
      - Presentation Outlines, 1982 (Box 33, Folder 8)
      - Re SEQ- BASIC A, 1982 (Box 33, Folder 9)
      - Sandelin, Marcus, 1982 (Box 33, Folder 10)
      - Scannel, Terry, 1982 (Box 33, Folder 11)
      - Schill, John, 1982 (Box 33, Folder 12)
      - Star User Interface, 1982 (Box 33, Folder 13)
      - SU, 1982 (Box 33, Folder 14)
      - Telegraf, 1982 (Box 33, Folder 15)
      - Thinkpiece, 1982 (Box 33, Folder 16)
      - Tymshare, 1982 (Box 33, Folder 17)
      - USC, 1982 (Box 33, Folder 18)
      - Use of Computers..., 1982 (Box 33, Folder 19)
      - Use of Multple Networks, 1982 (Box 33, Folder 20)
      - Viewports, 1982 (Box 33, Folder 21)
      - Virtual Device Interface, 1982 (Box 33, Folder 22)
      - Voter, 1982 (Box 33, Folder 23)
      - Yourdon, 1982 (Box 33, Folder 24)
    - Alpha Files A-Z 1983
      - Misc. Unfiled, 1983 (Box 36, Folder 33)
      - ADD, 1983 (Box 36, Folder 34)
      - AST, 1983 (Box 36, Folder 35)
      - Athena Project, 1983 (Box 36, Folder 36)
      - Augment, 1983 (Box 36, Folder 37)
      - Bell Labs, 1983 (Box 36, Folder 38)
      - Business Plans, 1983 (Box 36, Folder 39)
      - Calendar, 1983 (Box 36, Folder 40)
      - DX, 1983 (Box 36, Folder 41)
      - EDP, 1983 (Box 36, Folder 42)
      - EPRI, 1983 (Box 36, Folder 43)
      - ESV, 1983 (Box 36, Folder 44)
      - Graphics, 1983 (Box 36, Folder 45)
      - Grist, 1983 (Box 36, Folder 46)
      - Index Jump, 1983 (Box 36, Folder 47)
      - Info/Corp Assets, 1983 (Box 36, Folder 48)
      - Intel, 1983 (Box 36, Folder 49)
      - J-Format, 1983 (Box 36, Folder 50)
      - Jou Design, 1983 (Box 36, Folder 51)
      - Key Tronic, 1983 (Box 36, Folder 52)
      - Knowledge & Fifth Gen, 1983 (Box 36, Folder 53)
      - Lons Papers, 1983 (Box 36, Folder 54)
      - Lowe, David, 1983 (Box 36, Folder 55)
      - MAC, 1983 (Box 36, Folder 56)
      - Magnum/Augment, 1983 (Box 36, Folder 57)
      - Meyer, N. Dean, 1983 (Box 36, Folder 58)
      - McAuto, 1983 (Box 36, Folder 59)
      - NY State, 1983 (Box 36, Folder 60)
      - NLS, 1983 (Box 36, Folder 61)
      - NP, 1983 (Box 36, Folder 62)
      - Office Concept, 1983 (Box 36, Folder 63)
      - Para, Calvin, 1983 (Box 36, Folder 64)
      - PC Terminal, 1983 (Box 36, Folder 65)
      - P-DPCS, 1983 (Box 36, Folder 66)
      - P-Prog Workshop, 1983 (Box 36, Folder 67)
      - Reactive Systems, 1983 (Box 36, Folder 68)
      - Rheingold, Howard, 1983 (Box 36, Folder 69)
      - RPC/UIS, 1983 (Box 36, Folder 70)
      - Scientific American, 1983 (Box 36, Folder 71)
      - Suspense, 1983 (Box 36, Folder 72)
      - TCS & S, 1983 (Box 36, Folder 73)
      - TD NP, 1983 (Box 36, Folder 74)
      - TD2, 1983 (Box 36, Folder 75)
      - Technology, 1983 (Box 36, Folder 76)
      - Textnet, 1983 (Box 36, Folder 77)
      - Tymkos, 1983 (Box 36, Folder 78)
      - W Current, 1983 (Box 36, Folder 79)
      - Xanadu, 1983 (Box 36, Folder 80)
      - XT Info, 1983 (Box 36, Folder 81)
    - Alpha Files A-Z 1984
      - Misc. Unfiled, 1984 (Box 30, Folder 43)
      - MDC, 1984 (Box 30, Folder 44)
      - ACM, 1984 (Box 30, Folder 45)
      - AFIPS, 1984 (Box 30, Folder 46)
      - AH, 1984 (Box 30, Folder 47)
      - Aspen User Guide, 1984 (Box 30, Folder 48)
      - Augment, 1984 (Box 30, Folder 49)
      - BAKUP, 1984 (Box 30, Folder 50)
      - Bannon, Liam, 1984 (Box 30, Folder 51)
      - Blissmer, Robert, 1984 (Box 30, Folder 52)
      - Business Plan, 1984 (Box 30, Folder 53)
      - CAD/CAM, 1984 (Box 30, Folder 54)
      - Cohen, Stanley, 1984 (Box 30, Folder 55)
      - Collaboration, 1984 (Box 30, Folder 56)
      - Comprehensibility, 1984 (Box 30, Folder 57)
      - Compcon, 1984 (Box 30, Folder 58)
      - Computer Annual, 1984 (Box 30, Folder 59)
      - Computer Museum, 1984 (Box 30, Folder 60)
      - Conference Presentation Audiocassettes, 1984 (Box 30, Folder 61)
      - CSCI, 1984 (Box 30, Folder 62)
      - Denmark Trip, 1984 (Box 30, Folder 63)
      - DIRKIT, 1984 (Box 30, Folder 64)
      - EDP Analyzer, 1984 (Box 30, Folder 65)
      - Emergent Parts of Augmentation, 1984 (Box 30, Folder 66)
      - E-Press, 1984 (Box 30, Folder 67)
      - European TNet Access, 1984 (Box 30, Folder 68)
      - Freeman, Edward, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 1)
      - Friedrich, Gerhard, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 2)
      - Gnosis, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 3)
      - Grid Blanks, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 4)
      - Harvard, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 5)
      - Help Search, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 6)
      - IC TOA LA, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 7)
      - IEEE, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 8)
      - Irby, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 9)
      - ISD, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 10)
      - IUCA, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 11)
      - Kermit Manual, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 12)
      - Kestral, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 13)
      - Kommunedata, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 14)
      - Larger Scope Evolution, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 15)
      - Laurel, Brenda, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 16)
      - Library, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 17)
      - Lisa Slide Gist, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 18)
      - MacFORTH, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 19)
      - Mumford, Enid, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 20)
      - Marca, David, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 21)
      - MDC, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 22)
      - McAuto, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 23)
      - MIT, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 24)
      - Office Automation, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 25)
      - Office Technology, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 26)
      - OSI Reference Model, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 27)
      - PC, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 28)
      - Perrone & Assoc., 1984 (Box 31, Folder 29)
      - Plog Grist, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 30)
      - Plotter, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 31)
      - Prentice-Hall, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 32)
      - Presentation Foils, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 33)
      - Publications, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 34)
      - Republish, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 35)
      - RT AUG-CMS, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 36)
      - St. Louis, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 37)
      - Script Text, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 38)
      - Sign Master, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 39)
      - Slides, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 40)
      - Sloan School, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 41)
      - SNADS, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 42)
      - Software Initiative, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 43)
      - Spirit Clippings, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 44)
      - SRI/AIC, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 45)
      - SU Book, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 46)
      - TDIR, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 47)
      - TDW, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 48)
      - Teleforum, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 49)
      - Terminal & Node Support, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 50)
      - TN Access, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 51)
      - Tym/Comm. Technical Reference, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 52)
      - Tymlink, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 53)
      - UK Microdata, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 54)
      - University of Washington, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 55)
      - Userdoc, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 56)
      - Wilson, Reese C., 1984 (Box 31, Folder 57)
      - Workgroup Computing, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 58)
      - Workplace Automation, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 59)
      - Workshop Cooperative, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 60)
      - Workshop Study Records, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 61)
      - XPER Measurements, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 62)
      - X Reach Project, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 63)
      - XT Programs, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 64)
      - Yankee Group IBM, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 65)
    - Alpha Files A-H 1985
      - Misc. Unfiled, 1985 (Box 35, Folder 46)
      - Draft Records for 1986 Paper, 1985 (Box 35, Folder 47)
      - Adams, John, 1985 (Box 35, Folder 48)
      - AI, 1985 (Box 35, Folder 49)
      - AIC-SRI, 1985 (Box 35, Folder 50)
      - Arnold, Clem, 1985 (Box 35, Folder 51)
      - Arnold, DC, 1985 (Box 35, Folder 52)
      - ATE, 1985 (Box 35, Folder 53)
      - Augment, 1985 (Box 35, Folder 54)
      - Augterm, 1985 (Box 35, Folder 55)
      - Book Order, 1985 (Box 35, Folder 56)
      - Bjorn-Anderson, Niels, 1985 (Box 35, Folder 57)
      - BTST, 1985 (Box 35, Folder 58)
      - Calendar, 1985 (Box 35, Folder 59)
      - Carter, Dave, 1985 (Box 35, Folder 60)
      - CHI, 1985 (Box 35, Folder 61)
      - Clem, 1985 (Box 35, Folder 62)
      - Comm-RINS, 1985 (Box 35, Folder 63)
      - Computer Language, 1985 (Box 35, Folder 64)
      - Computer Mediated Work, 1985 (Box 35, Folder 65)
      - CONNEX, 1985 (Box 36, Folder 1)
      - C-Relev Docs, 1985 (Box 36, Folder 2)
      - Crocker, David, 1985 (Box 36, Folder 3)
      - C Seq Exper, 1985 (Box 36, Folder 4)
      - Current Notes, 1985 (Box 36, Folder 5)
      - CVs, 1985 (Box 36, Folder 6)
      - Datamation, 1985 (Box 36, Folder 7)
      - Demo Support, 1985 (Box 36, Folder 8)
      - Dialog, 1985 (Box 36, Folder 9)
      - Diffusion System, 1985 (Box 36, Folder 10)
      - Digest, 1985 (Box 36, Folder 11)
      - Digital Signatures, 1985 (Box 36, Folder 12)
      - Directory Updates, 1985 (Box 36, Folder 13)
      - Disc Log, 1985 (Box 36, Folder 14)
      - Egberts, Chris, 1985 (Box 36, Folder 15)
      - Environments, 1985 (Box 36, Folder 16)
      - E Ext. Grist, 1985 (Box 36, Folder 17)
      - E RINS, 1985 (Box 36, Folder 18)
      - Film/Photo Loaners, 1985 (Box 36, Folder 19)
      - Foot Mouse, 1985 (Box 36, Folder 20)
      - Gdog Progs, 1985 (Box 36, Folder 21)
      - Gem, 1985 (Box 36, Folder 22)
      - G&Os, 1985 (Box 36, Folder 23)
      - Grabhorn, Paul, 1985 (Box 36, Folder 24)
      - Grist, 1985 (Box 36, Folder 25)
      - Handouts, 1985 (Box 36, Folder 26)
      - Hardeman, Beau, 1985 (Box 36, Folder 27)
      - Hardy, Martin, 1985 (Box 36, Folder 28)
      - HP, 1985 (Box 36, Folder 29)
      - Holt, Reinhart, 1985 (Box 36, Folder 30)
      - Hori, Shiz, 1985 (Box 36, Folder 31)
      - Hulteen, Eric, 1985 (Box 36, Folder 32)
    - Alpha Files I-S 1985
      - IEEE, 1985 (Box 34, Folder 36)
      - IFIP, 1985 (Box 34, Folder 37)
      - IFTF, 1985 (Box 34, Folder 38)
      - Interactive Fantasy, 1985 (Box 34, Folder 39)
      - International Data Corp., 1985 (Box 34, Folder 40)
      - ISO, 1985 (Box 34, Folder 41)
      - ISS Seminar, 1985 (Box 34, Folder 42)
      - Japan's Magnificent Obsession, 1985 (Box 34, Folder 43)
      - J Memos, 1985 (Box 34, Folder 44)
      - Jaques, Elliot, 1985 (Box 34, Folder 45)
      - Johanen, Robert, 1985 (Box 34, Folder 46)
      - Journal Entry, 1985 (Box 34, Folder 47)
      - Key Issues, 1985 (Box 34, Folder 48)
      - Lehman Brothers, 1985 (Box 34, Folder 49)
      - Lincicome, Donald, 1985 (Box 34, Folder 50)
      - Linkers Dialog, 1985 (Box 34, Folder 51)
      - Lowood, Henry, 1985 (Box 34, Folder 52)
      - Lundh, Yngvar, 1985 (Box 34, Folder 53)
      - Marcure, Judy, 1985 (Box 34, Folder 54)
      - MATE, 1985 (Box 34, Folder 55)
      - Management, 1985 (Box 34, Folder 56)
      - McAir, 1985 (Box 34, Folder 57)
      - MDAIS, 1985 (Box 34, Folder 58)
      - MDC, 1985 (Box 34, Folder 59)
      - Meyer, Dean & Assoc., 1985 (Box 35, Folder 1)
      - Meyer Publications, 1985 (Box 35, Folder 2)
      - Miller, Herman, 1985 (Box 35, Folder 3)
      - MIR, 1985 (Box 35, Folder 4)
      - Misc., 1985 (Box 35, Folder 5)
      - Mucci, Tom, 1985 (Box 35, Folder 6)
      - McAir, 1985 (Box 35, Folder 7)
      - McAuto, 1985 (Box 35, Folder 8)
      - McLaughlin, Barbara, 1985 (Box 35, Folder 9)
      - Names & Structure, 1985 (Box 35, Folder 10)
      - NASA, 1985 (Box 35, Folder 11)
      - New Sys Spec, 1985 (Box 35, Folder 12)
      - NP, 1985 (Box 35, Folder 13)
      - NSF, 1985 (Box 35, Folder 14)
      - Ontyme, 1985 (Box 35, Folder 15)
      - Pasteups, 1985 (Box 35, Folder 16)
      - Patterson, David A., 1985 (Box 35, Folder 17)
      - Patterson, Tom, 1985 (Box 35, Folder 18)
      - PC Programming, 1985 (Box 35, Folder 19)
      - PC Reference Information, 1985 (Box 35, Folder 20)
      - Phonelog, 1985 (Box 35, Folder 21)
      - Photo Loans, 1985 (Box 35, Folder 22)
      - Planner Network, 1985 (Box 35, Folder 23)
      - PNEW, 1985 (Box 35, Folder 24)
      - P-Nodes, 1985 (Box 35, Folder 25)
      - Poduska, Paul, 1985 (Box 35, Folder 26)
      - Postscript, 1985 (Box 35, Folder 27)
      - Presentation, 1985 (Box 35, Folder 28)
      - Prod Seminar, 1985 (Box 35, Folder 29)
      - Questors, 1985 (Box 35, Folder 30)
      - Rand, 1985 (Box 35, Folder 31)
      - Rheingold, Howard, 1985 (Box 35, Folder 32)
      - Reminders, 1985 (Box 35, Folder 33)
      - Richardson-Smith, 1985 (Box 35, Folder 34)
      - STL, 1985 (Box 35, Folder 35)
      - St. Louis Trip, 1985 (Box 35, Folder 36)
      - Scratch, 1985 (Box 35, Folder 37)
      - Seybold Group, 1985 (Box 35, Folder 38)
      - SHARE, 1985 (Box 35, Folder 39)
      - Shneiderman, Ben, 1985 (Box 35, Folder 40)
      - Sil Vall Club, 1985 (Box 35, Folder 41)
      - Stroll, Dave, 1985 (Box 35, Folder 42)
      - SU, 1985 (Box 35, Folder 43)
      - Sumex, 1985 (Box 35, Folder 44)
      - SUNY, 1985 (Box 35, Folder 45)
    - Alpha Files T-Z 1985
      - TC/NP, 1985 (Box 30, Folder 25)
      - TD, 1985 (Box 30, Folder 26)
      - TDIR, 1985 (Box 30, Folder 27)
      - Teleconferencing, 1985 (Box 30, Folder 28)
      - Teleforum, 1985 (Box 30, Folder 29)
      - Telex, 1985 (Box 30, Folder 30)
      - Time-Life Books, 1985 (Box 30, Folder 31)
      - Topics, 1985 (Box 30, Folder 32)
      - Understanding the Implementation..., 1985 (Box 30, Folder 33)
      - UCSD, 1985 (Box 30, Folder 34)
      - UAD, 1985 (Box 30, Folder 35)
      - Wanveer, L., 1985 (Box 30, Folder 36)
      - Watson, Dick, 1985 (Box 30, Folder 37)
      - Whole Earth, 1985 (Box 30, Folder 38)
      - Windows, 1985 (Box 30, Folder 39)
      - X Grist, 1985 (Box 30, Folder 40)
      - X-RINS, 1985 (Box 30, Folder 41)
      - XT NP, 1985 (Box 30, Folder 42)
    - Alpha Files A-M 1986
      - ACM, 1986 (Box 29, Folder 39)
      - AI, 1986 (Box 29, Folder 40)
      - AIC, 1986 (Box 29, Folder 41)
      - AICOM, 1986 (Box 29, Folder 42)
      - AKW, 1986 (Box 29, Folder 43)
      - Answer, 1986 (Box 29, Folder 44)
      - Apple, 1986 (Box 29, Folder 45)
      - ATE/VAX PCP, 1986 (Box 29, Folder 46)
      - Augment, 1986 (Box 29, Folder 47)
      - Bootstrap, 1986 (Box 29, Folder 48)
      - Belleville, Bob, 1986 (Box 29, Folder 49)
      - BOS Notes, 1986 (Box 29, Folder 50)
      - Bush, Vannevar, 1986 (Box 29, Folder 51)
      - CISR, 1986 (Box 29, Folder 52)
      - Carter, TD, 1986 (Box 29, Folder 53)
      - Cashman, Paul, 1986 (Box 29, Folder 54)
      - Community Authoring, 1986 (Box 29, Folder 55)
      - Copyright Clearance Center, 1986 (Box 29, Folder 56)
      - Corporate/Strategic, 1986 (Box 29, Folder 57)
      - CSCW, 1986 (Box 29, Folder 58)
      - DEC, 1986 (Box 29, Folder 59)
      - Defense Applied Information Technology Center, 1986 (Box 29, Folder 60)
      - Dialog, 1986 (Box 29, Folder 61)
      - Dickinson, Jacob, 1986 (Box 29, Folder 63)
      - Digestifier, 1986 (Box 29, Folder 64)
      - Discussions, 1986 (Box 29, Folder 65)
      - Diskette List, 1986 (Box 29, Folder 66)
      - Electrical Roadmapping, 1986 (Box 30, Folder 1)
      - Ereland, JD, 1986 (Box 30, Folder 2)
      - Filtered Views, 1986 (Box 30, Folder 3)
      - Five Keys, 1986 (Box 30, Folder 4)
      - Gordon, Robert M., 1986 (Box 30, Folder 5)
      - Graphics, 1986 (Box 30, Folder 6)
      - Grist, 1986 (Box 30, Folder 7)
      - Hall, David, 1986 (Box 30, Folder 8)
      - HU Tool, 1986 (Box 30, Folder 9)
      - ICL, 1986 (Box 30, Folder 10)
      - IFTF, 1986 (Box 30, Folder 11)
      - Implementation, 1986 (Box 30, Folder 12)
      - Intellicorp, 1986 (Box 30, Folder 13)
      - IRM Notes, 1986 (Box 30, Folder 14)
      - Key Logic, 1986 (Box 30, Folder 15)
      - Livermore Lab, 1986 (Box 30, Folder 16)
      - Lisa Slide, 1986 (Box 30, Folder 17)
      - Link Support, 1986 (Box 30, Folder 18)
      - Lowood, Henry, 1986 (Box 30, Folder 19)
      - MDC, 1986 (Box 30, Folder 20)
      - M, 1986 (Box 30, Folder 21)
      - Mitiken, 1986 (Box 30, Folder 22)
      - Minibase User Guide, 1986 (Box 30, Folder 23)
      - MIT, 1986 (Box 30, Folder 24)
    - Alpha Files M-Z 1986
      - Tech- Doc RINS, 1986 (Box 28, Folder 2)
      - University of Arizona, 1986 (Box 28, Folder 3)
      - Augment Survey, 1986 (Box 28, Folder 4)
      - Retire NP, 1986 (Box 28, Folder 5)
      - RINS-DEC, 1986 (Box 28, Folder 6)
      - Strawman Architecture Workshop, 1986 (Box 28, Folder 7)
      - MDC Transfer Charges, 1986 (Box 28, Folder 8)
      - MDC Strawman Report, 1986 (Box 28, Folder 9)
      - New Tools for Thought, 1986 (Box 29, Folder 1)
      - NIAC, 1986 (Box 29, Folder 2)
      - JCN, 1986 (Box 29, Folder 3)
      - NP General, 1986 (Box 29, Folder 4)
      - NSF, 1986 (Box 29, Folder 5)
      - OP Driver, 1986 (Box 29, Folder 6)
      - OPUS, 1986 (Box 29, Folder 7)
      - PC Disk, 1986 (Box 29, Folder 8)
      - PCW Communications, 1986 (Box 29, Folder 9)
      - Phone Meeting Notes, 1986 (Box 29, Folder 10)
      - PICA PTY Ltd., 1986 (Box 29, Folder 11)
      - Picodyne Corp., 1986 (Box 29, Folder 12)
      - Plan Scratch, 1986 (Box 29, Folder 13)
      - PortaCOM, 1986 (Box 29, Folder 14)
      - Presentation Records, 1986 (Box 29, Folder 15)
      - Press, Larry, 1986 (Box 29, Folder 16)
      - PDDS, 1986 (Box 29, Folder 17)
      - PROFS, 1986 (Box 29, Folder 18)
      - Rheingold, Howard, 1986 (Box 29, Folder 19)
      - 1986 (Box 29, Folder 20)
      - RLB, 1986 (Box 29, Folder 20)
      - STC Notes, 1986 (Box 29, Folder 21)
      - Samples, 1986 (Box 29, Folder 22)
      - Signatures User Guide, 1986 (Box 29, Folder 23)
      - Slide Copies, 1986 (Box 29, Folder 24)
      - Smart, Ronald G., 1986 (Box 29, Folder 25)
      - Standby, 1986 (Box 29, Folder 26)
      - Strawman Architecture, 1986 (Box 29, Folder 27)
      - Stroll, David, 1986 (Box 29, Folder 28)
      - Symbolics Symposium, 1986 (Box 29, Folder 29)
      - TD, 1986 (Box 29, Folder 30)
      - Tender/One, 1986 (Box 29, Folder 31)
      - Time Management, 1986 (Box 29, Folder 32)
      - TOP, 1986 (Box 29, Folder 33)
      - TWA, 1986 (Box 29, Folder 34)
      - UCB, 1986 (Box 29, Folder 35)
      - Vrancken, Bob, 1986 (Box 29, Folder 36)
      - WADC, 1986 (Box 29, Folder 37)
      - Wanveer, Lloyd, 1986 (Box 29, Folder 38)
    - Alpha Files A-M 1988
      - AAAI, 1988 (Box 33, Folder 57)
      - ACOM NP, 1988 (Box 33, Folder 58)
      - ASIP, 1988 (Box 33, Folder 59)
      - ATF, 1988 (Box 33, Folder 60)
      - Actions, 1988 (Box 33, Folder 61)
      - Aegerter, William, 1988 (Box 33, Folder 62)
      - Areospace Projects, 1988 (Box 33, Folder 63)
      - American Institute for Research, 1988 (Box 33, Folder 64)
      - Aphorism History, 1988 (Box 33, Folder 65)
      - ASD Property, 1988 (Box 33, Folder 66)
      - Arizona, 1988 (Box 33, Folder 67)
      - Augment, 1988 (Box 33, Folder 68)
      - BCDG, 1988 (Box 34, Folder 1)
      - BF Scratch, 1988 (Box 34, Folder 2)
      - Barrett, Edward, 1988 (Box 34, Folder 3)
      - Bootstrap, 1988 (Box 34, Folder 4)
      - CALS, 1988 (Box 34, Folder 5)
      - CSCW, 1988 (Box 34, Folder 6)
      - Capabilities, 1988 (Box 34, Folder 7)
      - Charts, 1988 (Box 34, Folder 8)
      - Computer Mediated Community, 1988 (Box 34, Folder 9)
      - CO/S, 1988 (Box 34, Folder 10)
      - Contacts, 1988 (Box 34, Folder 11)
      - CoTheory Proposal, 1988 (Box 34, Folder 12)
      - Culver, Craig, 1988 (Box 34, Folder 13)
      - CV- Trev, 1988 (Box 34, Folder 14)
      - DEC, 1988 (Box 34, Folder 15)
      - Dialog Examples, 1988 (Box 34, Folder 16)
      - 5047, 1988 (Box 34, Folder 17)